Was that it, grade One sorcerer?
You did well running around,
but you're at your
limit now, aren't you?
(resigned sigh)
Unfortunately...
What?
His cursed energy's increasing?
Thanks to you.
I'm going to have
to go into overtime.
Overtime?
A time-based pact!
Was he limiting his own
cursed energy until now?
So much fun!
My cursed technique
draws a line along the target
and using a ratio
of seven to three,
then creates a weak point
at exactly that location.
I can create this
line along more
than just their full
height or wingspan.
And I can designate
it along various parts,
such as the head, upper
arm, forearm, and so on.
This cursed technique can affect
more than just living
creatures, as well.
He's revealing his technique?
You're serious huh?
At present--
The first way I can see to
exorcise this cursed spirit
is to continue damaging him
until he runs out
of cursed energy.
However, that's not
sustainable for me.
The second way is to
reduce him to smithereens
with a single blow.
Ratio Technique: Collapse!
What power!
And was that really
cursed energy I felt,
racing through it!
No way!
It's an expanded technique
that imbues the destroyed
target with cursed energy!
And, it's a wide-range attack
that probably puts
him at risk, too.
So...
I guess I should dodge this!
I'm going to withdraw.
You should get that
leg healed up quickly.
If we're both still alive,
let's meet up again.
Huh.
Huh?
(Opening Theme Music)
"Episode 11: Narrow-minded"
Huh?
Did the ground just shake?
Yeah, it did.
Intensity Two or so?
(phone ringing)
Damn it!
Ijichi's not answering!
I probably shouldn't
even talk to you.
Hm?
Is it really okay for me
to be asking him
questions like this?
How much am I allowed to
reveal about Jujutsu Tech, anyway?
[Phone Voice] The
person you have called,
is not available at this time.
[Itadori] Pick up, damn it!
(laughing chittering,
warbling sounds)
Come back here you little curse!
Ahh, I can't believe that guy!
What's going on?
[Junpei] A button
with a swirl on it.
So.
If you happen to meet
someone wearing a button
with a swirl like this,
then be friendly to them.
Because they're
jujutsu sorcerers.
I'm sure you'll find
that you get along.
But, the jujutsu sorcerers
are Mahito's enemies,
aren't they?
Aaargghh, forget it!
I'm just going to ask!
So then.
You were there in the theater
the day those guys got killed.
Huh?
Did you happen to see anything?
Maybe a weird
little thing like this?
Uhh. No.
Afraid not.
I've just started seeing
those things recently.
Gotcha.
Well I've got nothing
else to ask you then!
That was all?
But if you don't mind
could you wait until
the other guy shows up?
He's kinda like my boss.
Okay sure.
Cool, thanks!
So, what was showing
at that theater?
It was a repeat
screening of an old movie.
But I doubt you've
ever heard of it.
Aaaah, come on, try me.
[Junpei] Human Earthworm Three.
That movie was super boring!
I got punched so many
times over that one.
You got punched?
It was boring.
But after all it's
just a splatter film.
So maybe it's our own fault
for expecting it to
deliver any more than that.
Mm-hmm.
But Two.
Two was actually a
pretty good one wasn't it?
Yeah!
Yeah it was!
It was the only one
you could actually enjoy!
[Itadori] What do
you mean enjoy?
We've got him.
Well, you probably have
to watch the whole series
one after the
other to really get it.
[Junpei] At first glance,
Human Earthworm Two
looks like it's not
going to be any different
from One or Three.
But, in the end, it captures
the changing emotions
of the perfectionist who
abandons everything.
(fright gasp)
[Man] Mama.
[Itadori] Ah, so that's
why I was able to get
-through Two.
-Why, Mom?
At first, I couldn't understand
what was so good about it.
So I watched it
three more times.
And that wasn't easy
'cause the gory scenes
are pretty realistic.
You're really serious about it.
Do you like movies, Itadori?
Well, I've had a reason to watch
a lot more of them lately.
But I haven't been going
to theaters to see them.
Wait, why not?
The emotional impact of seeing
a good movie at
the theater is huge.
Even if on-demand
ones are more convenient.
I can't even remember
the last time I did that.
You should take me the
next time you go to one.
Huh?
[Itadori] Oh, you
need my number?
Go ahead.
Wait, how do I
add friends again?
[Nagi] Oh Junpei!
there you are.
[Junpei] Mom?
How unusual to see you out here.
That a friend of yours?
Actually we just met.
Yeah, but we have
a lot in common!
So I think we're
gonna be good friends!
Really?
Well, I hope the two of
you become fast friends.
[Junpei] Mom!
Hm?
We agreed...
You promised me
you'd quit smoking.
Oh, right, sorry.
I did promise not to smoke
in front of you anymore.
So what's your friend's name?
I'm Yuuji Itadori.
You know, you look
weird with green onions.
Oh, you think so?
I don't really wanna be a
green onions type of woman!
What are you talking about?
[Nagi] Yuuji, would you
care to join us for dinner?
Wha-? No, mom!
Quit bothering him!
Oh yeah?
Are you saying my
cooking is a bother?
-Huh?
-Hm?
"Rumble"
Are there any
foods you don't like,
or anything you're allergic to?
[Itadori] Nope!
("hoo boy!" whistle)
Huh?
(laughter)
It turns out that sorcerer
is a whole lot
crazier than he looks.
The two of you
went at it quite hard.
Getou!
That guy was interesting.
I learned a whole lot from him.
Oh?
I learned even if I'm pulverized
I won't die as long as I
maintain my soul shape.
Cursed energy consumption
counts toward supplementation.
It looks like there's
really no risk to me.
No matter how much I tweak
the shape of my own soul.
Next time I'll let loose
and try all kinds of things.
Getou.
Some clothes?
No, sorry.
Where'd your opponent go?
I don't know.
He just told me he
was going to withdraw.
But he might've gotten buried.
What?
You're at Junpei
Yoshino's house?
That's a bit risky!
[Itadori] I know, but it's fine.
Gotta go, we're
about to have dinner.
You're having dinner?
I'll head over to you at once.
If you sense trouble, get
out of there immediately.
Even if Junpei was involved
in the theater murders,
I doubt he's capable
of killing Itadori.
But still, as his supervisor
this is a huge
blunder on my part.
I can get away with it with
Gojou, as laid-back as he is.
But if the adult of
adults, Nanami, finds out,
he'll chew me a new one!
I'll probably burst into tears!
I've got to get moving!
You don't want to cry
in front of others
at your age, do you?
(phone vibrates)
"Nanami Kento"
Ahhh, he wasn't supposed
to call me so soon!
He's gonna chew me out for sure!
Hello, I'm sorry!
Hm?
I've just sent you my location.
Please come and
pick me up a.s.a.p.
I need you to take
me to Jujutsu Tech,
to get some
treatment from Ieiri.
[Ijichi] Treatment?
Nothing serious.
Nothing that's going
to kill me at least.
That's good.
Well, I'm about to
join up with Itadori.
Then we'll head your way.
[Nanami] What?
He's not with you?
Idiot!
Why'd you tell him that?
(short inhale into long sigh)
I had to really practice a lot.
You'll make the
perfect test subject.
Luck's really on my side.
That cursed spirit
is just a child.
It probably hasn't
been that long
since he sprang into being.
And he's greedily
enjoying his own growth.
The two special-grade
cursed spirits that Gojou fought
had mastered domain expansion.
If this one manages to survive,
it won't be much longer
before he reaches that stage, too.
On top of that,
his victim count far
exceeded our predictions.
Please, help me.
We need to exorcise
him as soon as possible.
Before it's too late.
(laughter)
[Nagi] What happened then?
So Takashi, he's all full of
confidence and he yells...
This is the larva
of a weird species!
It might even be poisonous!
Get back! Don't touch it!
So then of course
I picked it up,
and it turned out to be a
konjac noodle from lunch!
(uproarious laughter)
[Nagi] Wait, no way!
Konjac? It was just
a konjac noodle?
Mom, you've had
too much to drink.
[Nagi] Oh, you are funny, Yuuji!
She's the worst kind of drunk.
Wilson!
Forgive me, Wilson!
Ha ha!
That's from Castaway, isn't it?
That's right!
Is that from a movie?
I don't get it.
It's fire!
(laughter)
(soft sleeping or snoring)
Your mom's really cool.
And nice.
Mm-hmm.
[Nagi] Staying home
from school again?
(sad sigh)
It's okay.
You don't have to go.
Huh?
All you kids at your age,
you tend to take these
things too seriously.
If you think about it,
school is just a tiny aquarium.
After all, there's a
whole ocean out there.
Swim where you want to swim.
Hey, that was a pretty
cool thing to say, wasn't it?
What a brilliant saying!
Way to go, me!
(chuckle)
So hey, tell me about your mom.
What's she like?
Well I...
I never really got to know her.
Though I do have a few
faint memories of my father.
Fortunately, I had my grandpa.
(phone vibrates)
Oh!
Gotta take this call.
Hey there, Ijichi.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Actually, we were just
about to watch a movie.
Okay.
Two hours from now,
-got it.
-Two hours!
[Junpei] Itadori.
You're a jujutsu
sorcerer, right?
Yeah.
Should I have said that?
[Junpei] Have you
ever killed someone?
Hm?
No.
Someday, you'll have to fight
bad jujutsu sorcerers, right?
What will you do then?
If that happens, I still
won't wanna kill them.
Why not?
They're bad people.
I just think, if I
killed anyone,
the very option of killing
would then have forced
its way into my life.
The value of life would
become ambiguous.
I might start taking the
people I care about for granted.
And that scares me.
People don't have hearts.
That idea saved me.
It gave me strength.
But, if killing someone,
would mean tainting my soul,
(sighs)
then I can't kill anyone.
(gradual moaning, waking
into yawning and inhale)
Whoa, I fell asleep.
I guess Junpei's friend
must've gone home already.
Look at the time!
I need to clean up.
Hm.
Huh?
What is this?
Eww!
A finger?
"Jujutsu Kaisen"
"After the Satozakura
High School Incident"
[Ijichi] After the incident
at Satozakura High School,
we discovered the corpse of
Junpei Yoshino's mother, Nagi,
at their home, along with an
unsealed finger from Sukuna;
the pinky finger from
his second left arm.
We believe Nagi
Yoshino was attacked
by cursed spirits drawn
there by Sukuna's Finger.
Her remains were completely
missing from the waist down.
There were no visible
or detectable traces
of blood found on-site.
The victim's body was
found lying in her bedroom.
When the blanket covering
the corpse was pulled down,
there were only cold packs
and ice bags beneath the torso.
You're saying I'd just get
in your way, aren't you?
It's you that got hurt!
Next time take me with you!
My partner died.
But I wasn't with him
when it happened.
Why not?
Well, because I'm just a child!
You're a strong kid,
so try to help others.
Not again!
I have to go!
You can't.
As you have seen,
this patchwork cursed
spirit we're fighting
uses transfigured people.
There are some people
who are beyond saving.
If you continue with this work,
there will come a time
when you're forced
to kill a person yourself.
But this is not that time.
If that happens, I still
won't wanna kill them.
And that scares me.
Please understand this.
Being a child is not a sin.
And so for now,
I'd like you to continue
monitoring Junpei Yoshino.
I don't own any black clothing.
So I opened my mom's closet
and put on the first
thing that caught my eye.
The smell of the morning air,
and getting myself to
school were all familiar.
But today...
This is a cursed object
known as Sukuna.
Other curses are drawn
to it like a moth to a flame.
Yes but, what was
that doing in my house?
There are a lot of
curse users out there
who curse people for money.
It was probably
done by one of them.
If you have the money
and the connections,
it's easy to curse
someone to death.
Can you think of anyone?
Anyone who might hold a
grudge against you or your mother?
Or perhaps, someone
dark and gloomy,
with plenty of
money and free time?
And the certificate
of commendation,
and prize for the finest work
in the national book
report competition, goes to,
Shouta Itou!
(audience applauding)
Yay Shouta!
We love you Shoutah!
Stop it, that's embarrassing!
[Principal] Ahem.
Well, uh, we are extremely
pleased to have a student
from our very own school--
What did you do that for?
I told you to just
write whatever,
and here you wrote some
crap that won me this prize.
You wanna die?
No.
Sorry.
And, you didn't
win shit for yourself.
Shouta's just too cool
for school isn't he?
Yeah, no doubt!
You think?
Well I'll give him props
for being rich anyway.
Huh?
What's that black
thing in the sky?
[Male Student]
Whoa, that's weird.
Emerge from
darkness blacker still.
Purify that which is impure.
Hey, I did it.
Mahito, well done.
I can't afford to leave
any residuals of me behind.
What are the veil's effects?
[Mahito] No one can
escape from inside.
Some can enter from outside,
but only those with
weak cursed energy.
It's an unannounced
veil, in a residential area.
So the windows will
report it right away.
I do hope this all plays out
the way you believe it will.
I think it'll go just fine.
The course of events
was already set,
as soon as Junpei
landed Sukuna's vessel.
I'll cause the two
of them to clash,
and force Yuuji
Itadori into a pact,
giving Sukuna dominance.
I only wish Jougo was as calm
and level-headed as you are.
But it's cute how
straightforward Jougo is.
And are you good with this?
That finger, was kinda precious.
It's fine.
Yuuji Itadori easily
absorbed the finger
from the juvenile center.
As for the one we
planted at Junpei's house...
Let Jujutsu Tech find it.
Ah.
Another ploy?
Of course.
Well, have fun, I'll be
taking my leave now.
Wait?
You're not staying?
You should really
hang out and watch.
It's going to be
quite a bit of fun,
seeing all these
foolish kids die.
Ungh!
What the hell?
What's wrong with you guys?
Get up kids!
Are you okay?
[Junpei] They're not dead.
Huh?
Yoshino?
What's going on?
Do you know about this?
Do you know what happened here?
Teacher...
Just watch and you'll see.
Those...
Those scars!
The pain I had to go through,
you're going to feel it now.
Yoshino?
I have one question for you.
Are you the one who left
that thing in my home?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
What is this?
How are you doing that?
Wrong answer.
What makes you think
you're in a position
to answer my question
with your own questions?
You are going to die.
Whether your
answer is yes or no.
After all, I don't
have a technique
to see through your lies!
And believe me,
you've already done more
than enough to earn your fate!
So in your final
moments at least
-show some sincerity.
-I'm so sorry.
And?
Say it, you bastard!
(horrified gasp)
What are you doing?
Stop, Junpei!
Jujutsu sorcerer, back off.
(Closing Theme Music)
[Nobara] The layout's great,
but a three-burner
range portends death.
Set it ablaze, Mt. Hiei!
Matsutake for aroma,
shimeji for flavor!
The tones of autumn disappear
along with the
tears of the beloved!
Next on Jujutsu Kaisen:
Episode Twelve, "Bloody
Autumn Leaf-viewing."
The hunt is on for your heart.
(upbeat instrumental music)
"Episode 12: To You, Someday"